Hello, welcome back from Henry.
We're here at Dan Goldman. Thanks to
everyone, especially Part Time
Ale Janis and Cel.
And what's your name?
This is a very exciting time. I
love it because we've finally reached the point
where we're going to talk about Wichita. After
10 years of working on this
book, we've finally reached the point where we're going to talk about Wichita.
We've done 36 retreats over the past
10 years, and this is the
37th edition, both on air and online. I
feel like we're in a
tub, experiencing impermanence,
suffering in all realms, and
things like that.
Finally, we get to talk about
beautiful things like willpower and being a fashion
designer.
So we're mixing in yesterday's stuff.
This is a tool used by
Buddhist teachers where they sell you
an idea, like in the US, like when they're
selling a car. You go to a
place, and the people are very nice,
and when you leave, you feel like you're doing
something patriotic, like buying that car.
Skype that the people selling the cars are
bodhisattvas and just want you to...
That you have that car,
this
is very difficult not to be able to hear them, they are
very convincing, that's what they do,
judging immediately, and they know how to
talk to you
[Music]
from the first time in any form, it's
a tradition of Buddhism that you
come up with a great idea and talk about how
amazing it is,
and I think we're going to enjoy this anime
in particular because it's
all about a sales pitch about
why getting the medicine Buddha is so
amazing, because it's so amazing to have a
medicine Buddha, for me it's fun and a
very fun retreat, and today I think we're going to
have a special class after
this class, now we're going to have a
special discussion between me and Dr.
Wood about the Medicine Buddha's practice
and where it fits in
with what we're studying now,
we're going to do an hour of that and then
we're going to come back with the benefits of the medicine Buddha, I
think it's important, I'm, I'm
fortunate because I wasn't a Buddhist
when I first heard these teachings, I had just
arrived in Asia, I was in my
first classes, there was
a gay man teaching about holding it in,
and he had a translator
in the Vallobin lineage, and
I didn't know anything, he says
There were about 20 people from different
countries. We didn't know anything,
so there were a lot of
misunderstandings at first.
The translator was very young, and someone
had a very strange eastern dialect from
Tibet.
So it was all a learning process, like, through
misunderstanding. We would learn
words, and we would all talk about it the
wrong way for a couple of
weeks. Then finally, I wouldn't even
say, "No, I've realized, and she's not that
kind of girl." It's one of those words
that took us a few months to figure out. What it is, it's
not "body," which means sharp, and "
chita" means mind.
Everyone called it the enlightened mind, a
Buddha mind, and it was confusing because you're supposed to
acquire it. You're
not supposed to study to
become a Buddha, but if you have it, how are you
not a Buddha if you've already been a month and you
already have a Buddha mind? It was very
confusing, this
whole transmission of Buddhism for
these people from the Himalayas, those who
reached the Himalayas. We know some
arrived by truck through Iran and
Turkey, and we really didn't know what
was going on, and it took so long to
figure it out.  bowlers, which no longer
means the mind of a Buddha, it means
the desire to become, which
means the desire, the aspiration to
become you, but then they were
saying, that's why I come to the Himalayas, that's why I had
diarrhea all this week,
because
[Music]
because I have the desire to become
a Buddha, so because I have to
study, that's why I'm here, and they were
saying, 'no, there isn't, there's the real one and there's
the almost real one, it's
the little ball of
sugarcane skin that tastes sweet but it's not
really a little bottle, so bodies, and there's
our mind of a Buddha, and the mind
of a Buddha means that I want to be a
mind of a hula, and there's one that's real and there's
one that's not real, there's a mind of
doubt that I want to make that is real and another
that isn't, we got confused,
the translator didn't speak much English, I don't
know, but we learned it better because
nobody understood anything and we have to
decipher things that way, we learned,
I think there's a point here, there's
a point where you have the real
desire to become a Buddha, and then there are
some  Predictions
have to be a direct
cosmic experience. Something has to happen, perhaps
while your channels are open,
perhaps while your prana is flowing
freely, perhaps after perceiving
emptiness you directly obtain debod and
cheita. Before or after that, and there is, as it already
exists, a super body cheita where
you can see all beings in the world,
in the universe, or something like that.
All these questions arose, and we're going to
try to talk about them. And I think the
first thing we have to say is that
body cheita doesn't mean you're already enlightened.
Body cheita is what makes you... You're going to see
10 different points of sale from the
little shop, and as we go through
the different
announcements, you're going to start to understand what
's best. And the first way to approach
this traditionally is to realize how
incredible it is to have it. I
think it's going to be
a very fun retreat because it's only
15 classes
of talking about how incredible this verb
of cheita is, how incredible it is to have that
in you,
and learning how incredible it is to
have it. And we're going to learn how to
obtain it, and it's not easy. And if you talk
about this...  In the retreat
about areas and gas that worked for
12 years in a cave to get body
cheetah and they say it's not easy, it's not
like you're going to listen to a retreat
and you're already going to have visitors, it doesn't require a
lot of work,
I think it's like learning piano, something
requires a lot of commitment and it's going to take
time and it's hard to justify and it's not like you
can just sit down and start doing it, they
take a lot of work, you have to put in the
effort, but they are worth it, these ten
incredible things that are going to happen if the
option is so, the first
incredible thing that happens to you, which we covered
in the previous class, the retreat number 36,
giant duco wayar, I'm
going to review the
original language because first, because it is a
great blessing, the teacher who taught
this text, Pavón Carricoches, in my
opinion, is probably one of the
best teachers and it's incredible, an
incredible teacher who was able to
teach normal people,
he was a gay man from my university, I want you to
think of the scene monastery,
make the best Tibetan monastery, I'm
kidding, wherever he is soon, and he will also
read a link, follow, I know it's my gadget level, it
wasn't the highest clear
to be, but he  He was a Link H,
perhaps called a second-level cache,
and he was known for his ability to
convey teachings to
ordinary people. So he was very
popular with ordinary people in
Tibet—farmers, herders,
business people, the military. He
was very famous because he had the ability
to speak to ordinary people
in any way. The book he
wrote, the teaching that God gave for 24
days, was dictated by Trillar Crespo Ch,
who was the teacher of my teacher
X.
And he is such a great writer and
a great thinker. I
think he spent ten years writing
and fixing the
transcription.
I think this book is the greatest example
of Tibetan literature there is.
This is the most incredible book written
in the Tibetan language. The language is the
greatest that was written between summer and
after that, because of the
political problems in Tibet, the level of the language
dropped. I think this is going to be the
greatest example of Tibetan writing that has ever
existed in history. I'm not going
to teach you directly from the book, and it's not just
for you; it's also for
future generations who might not
want to learn.
This tradition is going to be lost. My
teacher taught it for thirty
years. He taught it three times.
I was his assistant, his slave. I got to
listen all three times. I was the only
person who listened all three times
when he taught him. In any case, it was
an honor to be able to do that.
So, the first one we already covered in the
previous class
means beyond attention. It means
the great vehicle, people of great
abilities. We were talking about
mothers.
People who are mothers have more
capacity. I have been a mother in this life. I haven't
been a mother in being here,
but I have observed in this life
that mothers have more
capacity. They are more capable and able to help
more people.
They have the capacity to abandon
themselves to help others.
There is a second virus in Sedona, and it is the
baby virus. Everyone is having
babies, and in a way, it is very
annoying for me
because a translator is lost for ten
years. Then I have to put up with the
translators. The more
translations, the more the child is growing up.
But in another way, they gain something,
especially the men. They learn
something. They learn not to be selfish. They learn
to give themselves for someone else, and in the end, I
think it makes them a  Great translator, so it does
n't matter those 10 years of
bad translation,
but if you had a child and made those
sacrifices, then you're a
different person. That's like Mahayana Texas
Jung of, meaning that once
you get something other than a widget, once
you get that desire to
become a Buddha to
benefit all beings, you go beyond
adding, you're becoming a
different kind of person. And I do
n't know, the way I grew up in Princeton
studying Buddhism, Isabena and the
historical schools of beyond the
historical schools of China, plain of
trabada, in this video, it's a different school,
and I don't know, in Kingston it was like very dry, in
Princeton the difference between the
schools was very dry and boring, I
still remember how boring it was. So if
you tell me, "So if you
have this little ball, you're going to be beyond that," it's
not that exciting, just a
different school. You go from one school
close to another school close, wow,
and now you're more added, is
n't it? In the way of experience,
experiential, isn't it?
Matallana doesn't mean a history, a
different school of what  What it means
is that you join a very select group of
people,
a very unusual group of
people, and we say it a little bit these
days, and we have this thing called the
Diamond Club.
When we were touring around the
world before the virus, there were
maybe 5, 10, 6, or 10 people in
each country who were
invited to join the Diamond Club, and they
were extraordinary people. These
people in different countries were
incredible
because, basically, you took the
10 most incredible people from 20
different countries and then judged them. If you
threw them together, it was a
special experience. What I'm trying to say is, you
take a country of 100 million
like Mexico,
or 1.4 billion people like China,
or 1.39 billion like India—I think it's
going to surpass China this decade
in terms of the number of people on YouTube—and
you take three or four of those
special people. This is going to be a
very unusual group of people. And if you take
maybe 10 people from each planet,
then think of it like Mahayana is
a  The club,
as it says, not exactly, but it's very, very
exclusive
to unusual people who have had a
certain experience, and that experience is
a direct Body Chita experience,
and that's all I want to say.
So, with the next 15 classes, it's one
thing: if you have this
real Body Chita experience,
then you have the experience of jumping from
planet to planet, billions of planets,
billions of giant inhabited planets.
You have this strange experience of
hopping from planet to planet and
meeting all living creatures
directly, all the fish, all
the birds, all the humans directly. You
know, sorry, a whole
world and establish a bond with them.
If you establish a commitment with them,
think of it like
hopping and committing, jumping from
planet to planet and making a personal connection.
I think there are 100 billion animals on
this planet,
for example, 80 billion or something like that. You
meet them directly, you make contact with
them, with each one individually,
and then you become... that experience
changes you. That's more... it's not a
school of Buddhism. That's not to say that there's
a personal connection with
countless millions of people.  of
bit beings,
and you've made a commitment to them, a
loving commitment similar to what
a parent makes to their child, a deepest
commitment to help them,
and that puts you in a special club, and that's
the first selling point.
[Music] It's that you're going to
join a very exclusive club. It does
n't mean excluding others; it's not
exclusive in that sense. It's just that if you
only learn these instructions and if you
only try to do them, then something will happen to you, something will
happen as a
being, and you're going to become a different
kind of being. You're going to become a being
beyond America. It's
like a different evolution of a
person into something higher. It's a being
that's close to God or something like that.
This is a very beautiful thing,
and it's a very small group that can
achieve it. Even just hearing the
instructions, even sitting
through these classes for the
next 10 days and hearing it is
extremely unusual. You have to be close to
this if you hear about it because
if you don't hear about it, they do
n't teach it at Princeton, you do
n't learn it anywhere else.
You have to be an unusual person, and you have to
be very close to the door
of the club to join that group.
To enter that
Mahayana clubhouse, you must be very close. If
you're listening to these instructions, so
open your mind, open your heart.
Listen. It sounds
impossible. It sounds like
Gisela, that's it. We're 10, but I'm not
that kind of person. I'm not special. I'm not one in
a million, not one in
10 million. I'm just me. I'm not that
special,
but Bass Pavón Carim Peche is going to
teach you why you are. And if you're
listening to this talk, now
the proof is that you are qualified
to be a planet jumper. You're
very close, by definition. You're very close
if you're listening to this
talk. So relax, learn the
instructions, and then try it. It's so much
fun. It's
incredible to jump from planet to
planet and meet everyone
and make this bond with them.
That means
without going from soul to soul. That's
the first argument of seeing you, and
we talked about it at the last retreat. Let's go to
the second. You have an image
for me. In the first order,
I like to call it joining the tennis team. I'm from
series,
and this means to me because I spent
many years  At school, trying to
get into the Werder Bremen club, there were only ten
people. I was number ten, and Nerio or
something like that, but I managed to get in. Here, it's like
an exclusive group of people, and that's the
kind of feeling I want you to
feel. If you work hard, you can get into
that team, and it's difficult and
requires hard work.
Let's go to the second benefit.
First, we'll show you the image. Please
see an image.
This is like having your postgraduate degree from
the university. It was funny when I
was at Princeton; I could
n't go to graduation because I had to work on a scholarship, and that was the last week of work. Then I paid off my debts the day I left in cash, and I worked three jobs for four years. Anyway, I didn't get to go to
graduation; I was just
setting up the tables for the toasts. I missed
that graduation moment.
But not too long ago, my friends in Mexico
invited me to the congress at UNAM. It
's the oldest university in
North and South America, and I think it has 30,000
students in total. So they
gave me a Johnson PhD there,
and I felt so  Honored to
receive a doctorate from Congress,
but then they taught me to call them
Doctor Roach. It
sounded really weird, Doctor Roach. And
really, not six doctorates after
that,
if you want, but it's the postgraduate degree after
my name. Even though I already had a
gadget, it felt good. It feels like a
great honor to go there
and wear a special suit,
and all these big cats, big fish,
all these big cats, big fish, and they
were giving us stuff, and we
became old, and that's where
Greens 3p came from, and it emerged in this attempt to
help all the kids in Mexico. But what I mean is, it's
nice to receive an exam, and it feels good
when they tell you, "You're gay, you have
a postgraduate degree,"
and that's the second benefit. When, when
the title
[Music],
to this word, marked, to these beautiful ones, I do
n't know about you, but there's a song
[Music]
in the hippie days that said, "
Beautiful passion," in the word "beautiful," for it
sounded so sweet, and we didn't know what it
meant,
but in a few words, very beautiful
sound, very beautiful. So I would like to be
called a policy phase. That's the second
benefit. People are going to call you a
Bodhisattva.  Breeze and you receive your
subtitle of Bodhisattva Jairo it reads it is
added your 2012 which sounds weird
there are duties to work hard to have
bowler because they are going to call you the
Bodhisattva to the calypso Bodhisattva Janis
and it sounds in the middle artificial gay he
is more important to be pretty than to have
the stock market title but it's
nice it feels good when someone
sees you as good
and it's the truth and it's the true thing
we tend to think that if someone is
a good person who makes coffee at
5 in the morning
[Music]
that person must be a savior but a
member of the club of people who
jump ships to planets and no I
am in the club of people who
jump to planets millions of
planets once
and to be recognized by someone else as a
savior
and to be called Bodhisattva that is a
thing that feels very good
especially if it is true it feels
incredible I like it and I am happy to
be Mr. Bodhisattva Gay Doctor
Roach
so let's go to the text let's go  Review
the text now.
I'm forcing you to review the
sixth one. I've been doing this for 10 years.
I've received 10 years of complaints from
people who don't want to review the text,
saying it's too difficult, they do
n't want to learn it, just teach me the
thing, I don't care, just shut up. I'm
going to teach you the text. It plants a great
seed in your mind. The people who
wrote these texts are Bodhisattvas, and
this is what they decided to write,
and it's incredible, it's incredible. So the
purpose of this retreat
is to plant seeds in your mind. You
probably won't decide to
take a body shower by the time
the retreat is over, but there will be seeds in
your mind that will open up, and you'll be
a knee-jerk.
And in fact, if you're the Bostonians, if you're
too foolish to sit and listen to all
these talks, you're going to receive
unstoppable seeds. So if you
sit down and take this retreat, you're going to
receive these seeds. How soon
depends on you, but you're going to get these
seeds. And many of the seeds are
transmitted through
active wisdom, through active books, and I
really think it's extremely
important that you  Feel
and take classes from a real one, and one
thing I can say without pride, without
exaggeration, is that this is a
true lineage. This lineage has been carried on for
2500 years, 100 generations, in a
pure way, in a very...  Oh, pure,
extraordinarily pure,
and if you just stay there, if you keep there,
you're going to become
a boli salva, and these are the
correct instructions, and they have a
true lineage, and we're honoring that
lineage by learning these ancient languages. You
don't have to learn Tibetan,
Sanskrit, Chinese, you don't, but
listening to it is a very powerful seed,
and you're going to get that experience much
faster. There's no
more fun experience in the world,
I think, except perceiving the macula
directly, than jumping from planet to
planet and meeting everyone in the universe. There's
nothing similar. Once you have
that experience, it's very difficult to
have a bad day. You can have a
half-bad day, but not a bad day.
[Music]
Who cares about anyone else,
anything else? And you've already met everyone in the
universe, and there's a commitment that
a mother makes to a child. How are you going to have
a truly bad day? Although, here we
go.
First, we have an appointment. Are you
ready with the Tibetan? There, here we go,
very good.
This year, right above that
means that here is the second
benefit, and it means that you have
the title of Mr. Gonzalo.  Mr.
was dying
if you get iancem which means body
cheetah if it arises in your heart
that chiqui in a single snap of the fingers
Corbett Sanz Roldán p
yes
a person who is chained in the
prison of Sans will make that they are chained
in a mortal body that is going to die and
that is going to be fixed
and that's what we real people talk about
when we get together we talk about
runners
[Music]
there I have this new doctor so
we are chained to this body yes yes you are
50 or 60 you don't know what I
'm talking about but you will reach this
stage if it feels like you are chained
to a mortal body that exist in a
single
even a person who is chained to
a mortal body young men's
what do those poor people who
are chained mortal efforts mean we
call it a daughter or a son of the
mockery even if you are in each one gives a
mortal body that is dying if your
body is not falling apart yet the
worst thing is that they were and you know why
because if it is if you breathe you are
collapsing it
becomes  More obvious after a
while, but even those people who
are chained to a body that
is collapsing, that is dying, if
they could have this body
cheetah experience, all the rumors say, "
That's a sure thing,
that's my daughter, that's my son."
[Music]
Even though you are chained to a
body that is dying, the doubters
are so proud of you, "That's my
son."
This is the second benefit of calling them
Bodhisattvas,
and the pse, Jose, the son of the mutes, the
son of the victorious, Judas, pretty, the
name is a very pretty name. They
leave the gamer, alcohol,
so I would say the next image,
if you are the land
of a father embracing his daughter,
and that's how I imagine it, it's
not that you have a piece of paper, it's that you are an
official Bodhisattva. Now you can
attack. If it is written that the Buddhas
gave you their title, and now you can
add it to your titles, it's innate. It's not
just this, but you enter a new
family and you have a new status.
There is the Mayan law.
[Music]
Scream,
so I like this version.  I
like to imagine that this father is a
Buddha and that he is embracing... I know he is
embracing his daughter or his son. His
body saves his new dressmaker. It's
incredible, it's incredible that you have
a new title and I call you dressmaker, that's what it is, that
's incredible. But for me, what
's more important is that you become part
of the family, which means you become an official son or daughter of the family. It's like a mafia family, people, you joined the family, you're in the family now, it's already a path or something like that, you're part of the family.
And show me how this feels, that the
enlightened beings of the world, who I know, if they're
sitting on the beach with you, they
hug you and are so happy because you're
part of the family. And that, for me,
that's more important than the title
Bodhisattva. If you're a modest one, but more
important, you're a Chinese Putin, wow, you
're their special child and they hug you like that. And to be hugged
by the Buddhas and to be
called their child is a
beautiful experience, to join that family,
to be recognized as a member of the
new family, like you married into the
family.  The Buddhas are an incredible feeling,
by the way. That tape above was from
the guide to the demonized lifestyle of
more tension and BBVA,
and in these sections, Pabón Carricoches
is going to rely
quite a bit on Antidiva Masters where they
talk about the benefits. In his
book, it talks about making the benefits
of the knee strike, so Pabón is Ripoche.
Many of the quotes were going to be taken
from Santi's work on Batman,
and if you can study the work of the
earth, it's extremely important. Those
are the courses, and yes, there are 10, 11, and 12, and they are
very important. You have no excuse
not to study them. By the way, I've been
receiving a lot of questions, and
well, now that you've given us, and I'm hiding it,
and the hunger and the mix classes aren't too
bad. Since the night, I
start to feel overwhelmed, and I say, I don't care,
okay? It's
better to be overwhelmed than to die, so I do
n't care. You have to eat as much as I
can feed you.
You have to do it. I'm sorry, I
'm remembering a moment
in my diamond business career
where the company owner arrived and  He
asked me how long it takes to buy 10
billion here.
In fact, they're complaining about the subway taking
two weeks. Well, it takes me like two weeks. I
want it in 24 hours. I
told him, "You can't buy 10,000 diamonds
in 24 hours, it's not possible." And he told me
FedEx, that the delivery guy delivers 25 packages
in one night, you can buy 10,000
diamonds in 24 hours. And he just
said, "It's not possible." Go back and teach me, teach me,
assistant. Your title here is if you're
a manager. Then you're
organized, and he left
his manager's office. So organize yourself, you're a little bit,
so you have to deal with that. You're going to
receive a lot of teachings. You should
be happy, you shouldn't be
complaining. Someone complained to me that
if I live in a tent,
all the courses you wrote
require a lot of space, I don't have time
to live. Well, I don't care, sleep
outside. I mean, God, you have to face
this. If you're a manager, well,
organize it. Later on, you'll
thank me. All parents say that. Later on, you'll
thank me. There's a
very famous line here.
[Music]
If you're someone who's in their 60s,
very famous, it's
part of the ceremony, devotees
demonized, in fact, if you just say that
line that supposedly can reinforce,
get the vows of body saga, at
least it's a picture of the commitment,
they want to get out of there,
today I have joined the beautiful family of
the seekers, let it be known that I have become
a child of the Buddhas,
and that's another very famous line
about a lesson, if I should, I want to read you the
whole line,
your version, which is not the version that
is used today, it's Tibet, it
's not in the sixth game,
and finally I did something useful with my life,
and now you can say that I have truly had
a human birth because I know
that because today I joined the family of
the Buddhas,
I became a child of the Buddhas today
because I took my wedding vows and zarba,
and now I have an extra responsibility,
and I have to conduct myself in a way
that reflects well how my
family conducts itself, I cannot embarrass my family, I have just been
accepted into a new family,
now I am a member of the family of
the Buddhas, a member of the clan bureau
of the  Buddhas, I have a new opportunity
to embarrass my new parents if
I act selfishly,
if I don't sacrifice myself, if I don't sacrifice
my desires for others,
then I will embarrass my
family and they will wish for it.
Therefore, I promise
that I will never adulterate my family. I
mean, if you make someone a
really rich cappuccino and accidentally spill something
like motor oil on it,
that's like you're adulterating it with
some garbage. Those Savoy notebooks,
double the adulteration, adulterating the Buddhas' family
with my nonsense. I'm going to be a good boy. I'm going to
make my family proud
of me.
Okay, back to the tea, right?
They're not ready to pass.
Maybe that feeling of the raclette.
The big question in your cave, in your life,
is whether you were accepted into the family or not.
My machine, I do
n't care if you can read
other people's minds. I don't care if you can fly
in the sky. I don't care if you have
a doctorate in every subject in the
world. I don't
even care if you have
directly perceived that. I don't care if
your  Little piggy,
if you don't have this attitude,
where we call Buddhists, where can they
call Buddhists? You can perceive
emptiness and not be a police officer, you can
fly through the sky and our soul
can heal people and not be a
bodhisattva and not be a child of
doubt.
[Music]
And we can say that you haven't joined the
family yet, have you jumped into the worlds or not?
That's the question. Next paragraph:
Who do I like? This is the image of this
very handsome animal,
but that's a donkey. Donkey,
donkey, it's different, it's a
mule. In the painful, keep, keep
the bike.
If you have a little ball in your heart,
Jackson notes,
and in what can be a dog, can be
a body,
and can be as dumb as a mule, a
donkey, but you're still part of the family,
and it means you've been accepted as a
member of the family. I love this
paragraph, and every paragraph of this text
is full of meaning. You could take
a paragraph, you could meditate on them
for a week. It was very difficult for me
to choose which paragraphs are most important. It's very,
very difficult. Every paragraph is
incredible and exquisite, so
this means...  Smith,
and we're all human, we all make
mistakes, but if you spend your whole life—
which I have—trying to be a good
person and you fail many times,
then you start to feel like an
idiot, or like a donkey, like a horse.
You feel like a spiritual idiot
because you really tried, and yet
you have bad habits you can't
eliminate and bad attitudes you can't get
rid of. And many dramas
go through their lives trying to fix you, and you
still feel like an idiot.
So there is hope for Monterrey,
because it is said there is hope. Even
you who have tried so many times for so many
years to improve
and feel like you haven't made
much progress can still be part of the
family. We love you, and we
especially enjoy
welcoming into our family
people who have bad habits they can't
eliminate. But while this is happening on
some planets, you can be in
the family. You don't have to be perfect
to be in our family. You do
n't have to be perfect to be a
tailor for a visa. You are studying
how to be perfect, but you are not perfect
yet. The reason you become
a Body Saver is to learn how to
be perfect. So we love you,
Body Savers.  Imperfect waters because if you are a
perfect body save you are a Buddha and we do
n't take doubts in the family, they are already
family.
We want body saves. Both
are people who are imperfect and who
have bad habits that they have been
struggling with for decades, many years,
and have broken all these vows that Sublime
gave them
and have not been able to do their
practice and Netflix took over their
minds. We love these people who are
the people we want in the family.
[Music]
We want to update those who are
trying to be good. Today we
welcome into the Buddha family
people who are perfect who want to be
seen dead, and that is what we really
want and that is the people we
are really looking for. So
let's stand here, let's stop here today,
sorry, let's take a break
and run for a coffee and go to the
bathroom and we'll be back in 10 minutes and
we're going to have a very good
conversation with the doctor about the Medicine
Buddha's medicine practice.
We'll see you Bodhisattvas in about 10
minutes.
Thank you.
[Laughter]